A Finding Aid to the Tibor de Nagy Gallery Records, 1941-2016, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Tibor de Nagy Gallery records
1941-2016
Archives of American Art
Tibor de Nagy Gallery
AAA.tibode
Archival Resource Key
43.9 Linear feet
3.26 Gigabytes
The records of the New York Tibor de Nagy Gallery measure 43.9 linear feet and date from 1941-2016. The records document the activities of the gallery through business records and correspondence, exhibition files, artist files, financial and legal records, inventory records, and a small amount of records of the Houston Branch.
Biographical / Historical
One of the earliest modern art galleries in New York, Tibor de Nagy Gallery was founded in 1950 by Tibor de Nagy and John Bernard Myers. Initially the gallery featured the work of second generation Abstract Expressionists and continues to operate today with a focus on the Post War second generation New York School.
John B. Myers served as the gallery's first director and De Nagy was the business manager while continuing to work in the banking business. Early on, the gallery introduced and promoted second generation Abstract Expressionists such as Grace Hartigan and Alfred Leslie. The gallery quickly earned a reputation for promoting the work of emerging artists, including Carl Andre, Helen Frankenthaler, Jane Freilicher, Red Grooms, Fairfield Porter, and Larry Rivers, among others, giving many of them their first solo shows.
Later the gallery gained a reputation as a space for collaborative artistic ventures and organized exhibitions that combined visual imagery and poetry by several New York School poets. The gallery also published books by poets John Ashbery, Frank O'Hara, and James Schuyler, as well as a poetry newsletter entitled Semi-Colon.
In 1973 de Nagy teamed with Marvin Watson to open the Watson/deNagy Gallery in Houston, which closed in 1983. Tibor de Nagy retired from banking in 1970 and continued running the gallery until he died in 1993. The Tibor de Nagy gallery continues operating today at 724 Fifth Avenue under the direction of Andrew Arnot and Eric Brown. It also works with a number of estates, including those of Joe Brainard, Rudy Burckhardt, Donald Evans, and Jess.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were donated by Tibor de Nagy Gallery in multiple accessions between 1993-1996 and in 2018. Additional material about the exhibition, Digital Explorations: Emerging Visions in art, 1988, donated in 2020 by one of the exhibition curators, Ligia Ercius-DiPaola.
Scope and Contents
The records of the New York Tibor de Nagy Gallery measure 43.9 linear feet and date from 1941-2016. The records document the activities of the gallery through business records and correspondence, exhibition files, artist files, financial and legal records, inventory records, a small amount of records of the Houston Branch, and exhibition announcements.
Business records include correspondence and administrative files. Business correspondence is with clients, curators, galleries, museums, colleges and universities, organizations, and publications, such as the Museum of Modern Art, Art Dealers Association, National Institute of Arts and Letters, United States Information Agency, The Hirshhorn Museum, Art News, Art in America, Pauli Hirsch, Jacqueline Kennedy, Charles Penney, Nelson Rockefeller, and many others. Correspondence concerns sales, purchases, shipping, loans, general exhibitions, publicity, events, publications and publishing, and other topics. Additional documents found within the correspondence files are purchase invoices, inquiries, shipping receipts, and photographs. Correspondence with artists is found in the Artist Files series. Administrative files concern day-to-day operations and include leases and construction documents, incorporation, insurance, art appraisals, art framing, and other general business affairs.
Exhibition files document many exhibitions held at the Gallery and include clippings and research materials, exhibition catalogs, exhibit and gallery plans, correspondence, and photographs, some in digital form. Some loan agreements and shipping receipts are also included.
Artist files document business affairs with individual artists and also contain collected information on artists. Typically, there are several files on each artist which may include printed materials, biographies, consignments, loans documentation, sales documentation, correspondence, photographic material, publicity, and reviews. Artists well represented among these files include Rosemarie Castoro, Ray Ciarrocchi, Robert Goodnough, Harold Gregor, Red Grooms (including a transcript of "A Conversation with Marison and Red Grooms"), Joyce Kozloff, Peter Reginato, Tony Robbin, Leatrice Rose, and Nancy Witteman-Widrig.
Financial records include incomplete runs of billing statements, expenses and cash disbursements, paid and unpaid invoices, and sales and shipping receipts. Inventory records consist primarily of index cards and/or sheets that document stock, consignments, loans, sales, and shipping.
A relatively small amount of Houston branch records include announcements, clippings, correspondence, financial information including consignments, income, invoices, and statements, photographs, publicity materials and a research file on Houston art museums.
Exhibition announcements promote the gallery's exhibitions for artists including Joe Brainard, Shirley Jaffe, Fairfield Porter, Rosemarie Castoro, Alfred Leslie, and many others.
Arrangement
The Tibor de Nagy Gallery records are arranged into seven series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Business Records and Correpondence, 1950-1993 (10 linear feet; Boxes 1-10)
Series 2: Exhibition Files, 1941-1992 (2 linear feet; Boxes 11-12)
Series 3: Artist Files, 1956-1993 (18.6 linear feet; Boxes 13-31, 46)
Series 4: Financial and Legal Records, 1951-1984 (3.5 linear feet; Boxes 31-34)
Series 5: Inventory Records, 1952-1989 (9 linear feet; Boxes 34-43)
Series 6: Houston Branch Records, 1969-1984 (1.2 linear feet; Boxes 43-45)
Series 7: Exhibition Announcements, 1953-2016 (0.8 linear feet; Boxes 47-48)
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Washington, D.C. research facility. Researchers interested in accessing born-digital records or audiovisual recordings in this collection must use access copies. Contact References Services for more information.
Related Materials
Among the holdings of the Archives of American Art are an oral history interview with Tibor de Nagy, March 29, 1976 conducted by Paul Cummings; the John Bernard Myers papers (which do not contain documentation of his work at the gallery); and the Watson/de Nagy Houston gallery records available only on microfilm, a small portion of which may also be duplicated in the original records described in this finding aid.
Art, Modern; Photographs; Art galleries, Commercial -- New York (State); Art galleries, Commercial -- Texas; Art in America; United States Information Agency; Art Dealers Association of America; National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.); Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979; Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.); Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden; Rose, Leatrice; De Nagy, Tibor, 1908-1993; Ciarrocchi, Ray, 1933-; Reginato, Peter, 1945-; Castoro, Rosemarie; Penney, Charles Rand, 1923-2010; Robbin, Tony; Witteman-Widrig, Nancy; Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1929-1994; Kozloff, Joyce; Hirsch, Pauli; Grooms, Red; Gregor, Harold, 1929-; Goodnough, Robert, 1917-
- Business Records and Correspondence, 1950-1993; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 10 Linear feet Boxes 1-10
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes business records, some financial records, and correspondence with business partners of the gallery including clients, colleagues, other galleries and museums, institutions, corporations, and publications. These materials reflect the ongoing business of the gallery from its foundation until Tibor de Nagy's death in 1993.
  Arrangement
  Arranged as 5 subseries:
  Missing Title
  1.1: Galleries, Museums, and Institutions, 1953-1991
  1.2: Clients and Colleagues, 1950-1992
  1.3: Publicity and Advertising, 1956-1989
  1.4: Administrative Records, 1957-1988
  1.5: General Correspondence, 1951-1993
  - Galleries, Museums, and Institutions, 1953-1991; 1.1; Archival Resource Key; 2.4 Linear feet Boxes 1-3
    Business correspondence with other art galleries, museums, university galleries and museums, corporations, and historical organizations. Enclosures document the transfer of artworks, either through purchase or loan, including invoices, contracts, agreements, photographs and shipping receipts. Correspondents include the Museum of Modern Art, Art Dealers Association, The National Institute of Arts and Letters, United States Information Agency, The Hirshhorn Museum, and foreign galleries.
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1964-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allen Memorial Art Museum, Oberlin College, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Federation of Arts, 1956-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Argus Gallery, 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Art Association of Indianapolis, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Art Dealers Association, 1961-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7-12)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, 1955-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Art Rental Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1957-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Art South, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Arte Centro, Milan, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Artists' Choice Museum, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Arts Club of Chicago, 1959-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Axiom Gallery, London, 1964-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Ball State University, 1959, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1959-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Bayonne Jewish Community Center, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bognar Gallery, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Brookhaven Laboratory, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Brooklyn Museum, 1956-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Carnegie Institute, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1971-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Chemical Bank, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Christie's, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Collectors Gallery, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Columbia Museum of Art, 1956-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1956-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1958-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - David Mirvish Gallery, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Dayton Art Institute, 1959-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Denver Art Museum, 1957-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Devlin Gallery, 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Dord Fitz Gallery, 1960-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Dwan Gallery, 1960-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Esther Bear Gallery, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1959-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Feigen / Feigen Palmer Gallery, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Felix Landau Gallery, 1962-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Finch College Museum of Art, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Franklin Siden Gallery, 1963-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Galeria Colibri, San Juan, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Galerie Darthea Speyer, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Galleria La Bertesca, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - German Galleries, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Gertrude Kasle Gallery, 1965-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gimpel Fils Gallery, 1961-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gres Gallery, 1959-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Guggenheim Museum, 1961-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Gump's Gallery, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - H.O. Gerngross and Co., 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Hamilton Galleries, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, 1974-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Holland Gallery, 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Houston Contemporary Arts Association, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1959-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Instituto Torcuato di Tella, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Jack Glenn Gallery, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - James L. Lodge Gallery, 1975-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Jefferson Place Gallery, 1959-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John Berggruen Gallery, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kansas City Art Institute, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Katonah Gallery, 1962-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Keene Bookshop and Gallery, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Knoedler, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Krannert Art Museum, 1960-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Lee Gallery, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Louisiana State University, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Corporation, 1967, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1960-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - McCleaf Gallery of Philadelphia, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - McNay Art Institute, 1972-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Meredith Long Gallery, 1974-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1955-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1957-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Moore College of Art, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1971-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1954-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34-37)
    - Museum of Modern Art Lending Services, Consignment Sheets, 1953-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Museum of Modern Art Lending Services, Sales Confirmations, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - National Association of Fine Arts Dealers, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - National Collection of Fine Arts, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - New School of Art Center, 1955-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - New Vision Centre Gallery, 1964-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - New York Cultural Center, 1967-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - New York University, 1959-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Newberry Farms Gallery, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Newport Jazz Festival, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Nicholas Wilder Gallery, 1966-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1957-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Nova Gallery, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Obelisk Gallery, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Olympia Gallery, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Parrish Art Museum, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Pasadena Art Museum, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Paul Facchetti Gallery, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1960-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Philbrook Art Center, 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Prentice Hall Publishing Company, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Purdue University, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Quay Gallery, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Reed College, 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Richard Gray Gallery, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Rose Art Museum, 1958-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Ruth S. Schaffner Gallery, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1963-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Simonne Stern Gallery, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Southern Illinois University, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - State University College, New York, 1955-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1972-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Swearingen-Byck Gallery, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Syracuse University, 1962-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Union College, 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - United States Information Agency, 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - University of Colorado, 1958-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - University of Illinois, 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - University of Kentucky, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - University of Minnesota, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - University of Nebraska, 1956-1964, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - University of New Mexico, 1963-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - University of Texas, 1971-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Vassar College, 1954-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1958-1966, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1959-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Walker Art Center, 1955-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Washington Gallery of Modern Art, 1962-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Washington University, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Watson Gallery, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Weatherspoon Art Gallery, 1970-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - West Publishing Company Collection, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Westmoreland County Museum of Art, 1966-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, Fairfield County, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Woodward Foundation, 1963-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Worcester Art Museum, 1965-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Yale University, 1959-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Clients and Colleagues, 1950-1992; 1.2; Archival Resource Key; 0.6 Linear feet Box 3
    Correspondence between the gallery and various customers and clients interested in specific artworks or artists as well as curators and other gallery owners. Documents include purchase invoices, inquiries, shipping receipts, and photographs. Correspondents include Pauli Hirsch, Jacqueline Kennedy, Charles Penney, Nelson Rockefeller, as well as Tricia Collins and Richard Milazzo.
    - Alexander, Brooke, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Baum, Jane, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Beard, Judge Edward A., 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bergman, E.A., 1964-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Booke, Stephen, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bortolazzo, Tom, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Carey, Ted, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cohen, Wilfred P., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Coleman, Dr. Jules, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Collins, Tricia and Milazzo, Richard, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Daniels, Alfred, 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - De Coninck, Suzanne, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Dotremont, Philippe, 1959-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Doyle, John, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Drake, Robert, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Duffy, James, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Fader, Ann, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Feiwel, Henry, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Finn, Gloria, 1961-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Friedman, B. H., 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Gates, Mrs. Clinton, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Godkin, Antoinette, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Gosman, Mrs. Joseph, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Gross, S.J., 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Heller, Ben, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Hirsch, Pauli, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Hirshhorn, Joseph, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Hoving, Thomas P.F., 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Johnson, Philip, 1950-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Kelley, Chapman, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Kennedy, Jacqueline, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Korjeff, Michelle, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Lee, Janie, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Le Maire, Eleanor, 1961-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - MacWhinnie, John, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Magerstadt-Fisher, Maggy, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Malone, Adrian, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Martin, Steve, 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Mayer, Robert, 1960-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 67)